ABRAHAM JOHN

Virtual assistant

+254758238617 Nyali ,mombasa,kenya jabrahamjohns@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/jabrahamjohns

EDUCATION

BSC MATHEMATICS AND COMPUTER SCIENCE, Technical

university of Mombasa.

09/2019-07/2024,

VIRTUAL ASSISTANT ALX

University Africa

05/2022-08/2022

Graduated and certified to work both remote. Onsite and hybrid as a VA worldwide

A-LEVEL DEGREE, limyounsim good people mission school 02/2016-11/2019,

Successful completion and attained the Kenya certificate of secondary education with a mean grade of B

O-LEVEL DEGREE, St. patricks

Neema Academy 01/2009-11/2015,

Successful took the course and attained the Kenya certificate of primary education with a mean grade of B+ SKILLS

- Customer focused service
- Customer experience
- Social media management
- Martial arts (taekwondo)
- Computer packages
- Programming skills
- Licensed driver
- Technical and soft skills

LANGUAGES

English (bilingual)
Swahili (intermediate)

SUMMARY

An adaptable student with the knowhow of application development, programming skills and database management not forgetting scheduling, organization and client and good customer service experience.

I am to leverage y skills to fill the vacancy at your company. Frequently praised for good communication dependability hard work and reliable to achieve set goals both individually and group settings

WORKING EXPERIENCES

Web designer and virtual assistant

2022 - PRESENT

AJ networks, Kenya

Am currently working as a freelancer and an intern on a part-time basis.

And my tasks and responsibilities include:

- ★ Maintaining a well-organized digital filing system and backups to reduce data loss.
- ★ Developing custom websites to meet clients' needs
- ★ Collaboration with web content editors to facilitate website maintenance
- ★ Mail and booking management for clients

Virtual and sales assistant

Swansea shop and wholesales

Work as time to time part-time VA and assistant at the stores to manage emails, social media and delivery of goods.

Sales and marketing intern

04/2022-06/2022-

Direct and perfect international, Mombasa

This position was an internship, and my tasks included

- Promotion of goods and products
- Sales and marketing of fast moving products

Skills and accomplishment include:

- Completion of training
- Sales skills and customer experience management

Events security guard 9/2021-12/2021

Wild waters, Mombasa

Was a part-time security events guard job aimed at impacting customer skills and service offering

- ➤ Accuracy skills and time management
- ➤ Attention to details whether large or small which is essential in every working details
- > Time management

VOLUNTEER WORKS

Crossroads fellowship

Volunteering for donations and supervision of donations under the annual anniversary celebrations

Community outreach

Volunteered in the annual adult and needy give away

Packaging.

Volunteered for food and donations packaging since I had the skills form my work experience

HOBBIES.

- Driving
- Coding
- Swimming
- Martial arts
- Watching
- Travelling
- learning

Sales and delivery persons 01/2020- 10/2020

Pakawa general stores

Worked as a sales boy and assistant for the goods and services provided by the company

- Keep store records
- Deliver goods to customer on order
- Update and keep track of stocks
- Unload goods at specific intervals when in place to do so Σ
- Cleaning and safety handling

Packaging 11/2020-1/2021

Moffataste cakes and pastry

Worked in the nightshift packaging department.

- Packaging skills
- Organization
- Attention to detail.

REFEREES

Meshach lodenyi, +254724267843

owner and manager Swansea shop

Nelly Wanjiru +254723264041

Pakawa general stores

Wild waters Kenya. +254726337000